{
  "title": "Rescueland Planets - very hard!",
  "listOfQuestions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the capital of Rescueland?",
      "correctAnswer": "Non-existent",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Erros", "The Great Computer", "Lumen City"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who leads Titan?",
      "correctAnswer": "Monoquia",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Zoltar", "Erros", "The Great Computer"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the atmosphere composition of Hermonochy?",
      "correctAnswer": "Hydrogen 86%, Helium 11%, Methane 2%",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Oxygen 60%, Nitrogen 30%, Argon 10%", "Nitrogen 70%, Oxygen 20%, Sulfur Dioxide 10%", "Oxygen 55%, Nitrogen 30%, Trace gases 15%"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How many interceptors does Ralfialand have?",
      "correctAnswer": "2200",
      "wrongAnswers": ["30", "5000", "2400"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the tech level of Klesone?",
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "wrongAnswers": ["9", "11", "12"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which planet is the most powerful superpower?",
      "correctAnswer": "Helucky",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Recola", "Rescueland", "Titan"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the capital of Bad Guy Land?",
      "correctAnswer": "Del",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Ilines", "Dakhem", "Gorath"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the atmosphere of Aquarion primarily composed of?",
      "correctAnswer": "Water Vapour 70%, Oxygen 20%, Nitrogen 10%",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Oxygen 55%, Nitrogen 30%, Trace gases 15%", "Oxygen 40%, Argon 30%, Carbon Dioxide 30%", "Nitrogen 70%, Hydrogen 20%, Oxygen 10%"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the leader of Recola?",
      "correctAnswer": "Emperor Astan",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Zoltar", "Monoquia", "Erros"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the population of Titan?",
      "correctAnswer": "7,200 trillion",
      "wrongAnswers": ["7.9 billion", "34.2 quadrillion", "800 trillion"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the tech level of N2?",
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "wrongAnswers": ["5", "6", "3"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary gas in the atmosphere of Glaciera?",
      "correctAnswer": "Oxygen 60%",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Nitrogen 30%", "Methane 25%", "Carbon Dioxide 20%"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who leads the Imperium?",
      "correctAnswer": "Xarendos",
      "wrongAnswers": ["King Coators", "Governor Ecard", "Luncil"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the main focus of Keluha's economy?",
      "correctAnswer": "Crystalline resources",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Agriculture", "Technology", "Mining"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the population of Yelthia?",
      "correctAnswer": "90 billion",
      "wrongAnswers": ["150 million", "50 million", "2 trillion"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which planet has the largest army size?",
      "correctAnswer": "Rescueland",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Helucky", "Recola", "Titan"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the power status of Aquarion?",
      "correctAnswer": "3800000000/6000000000",
      "wrongAnswers": ["2900000000/6000000000", "6000000000/6000000000", "5000000000/6000000000"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who governs the technology advancements in Recola?",
      "correctAnswer": "Emperor Astan",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Commander of War Weda", "The Great Computer", "Luncil"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the total ground force of Helucky?",
      "correctAnswer": "37 septillion",
      "wrongAnswers": ["37 trillion", "37 billion", "37 quadrillion"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the capital of Wana?",
      "correctAnswer": "Nezon",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Havenford", "Ironhold", "Fres City"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the tech level of Ukakia?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "wrongAnswers": ["7", "6", "9"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which planet is characterized by expansive forests and oceans?",
      "correctAnswer": "Wehaya",
      "wrongAnswers": ["N2", "Aquarion", "Helucky"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the atmosphere of Loaa primarily composed of?",
      "correctAnswer": "Oxygen 60%, Nitrogen 20%, Water vapor 15%",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Oxygen 55%, Nitrogen 30%, Trace gases 15%", "Oxygen 70%, Nitrogen 20%, Argon 10%", "Oxygen 50%, Nitrogen 40%, Methane 10%"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the main focus of the economy in Nara?",
      "correctAnswer": "Energy harvesting from storms",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Mining", "Agriculture", "Technology"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary gas in the atmosphere of Aquarion?",
      "correctAnswer": "Water Vapour",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Nitrogen", "Oxygen", "Helium"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the capital of the Mega Bad Guy Land?",
      "correctAnswer": "Ilines",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Dakhem", "Gorath", "Del"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the leader of Heloa?",
      "correctAnswer": "Luncil",
      "wrongAnswers": ["King Coators", "The Great Computer", "High Lord Tacer"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the tech level of Fufe?",
      "correctAnswer": "5",
      "wrongAnswers": ["6", "7", "8"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the power status of Imperium?",
      "correctAnswer": "6125487350/6000000000",
      "wrongAnswers": ["6000000000/6000000000", "4900000000/6000000000", "3200000000/6000000000"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the leader of Wonto?",
      "correctAnswer": "Tsar Protader",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Luncil", "King Coators", "The Great Computer"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the capital of Naha?",
      "correctAnswer": "Starlight Haven",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Fres City", "Havenford", "Filaga"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the atmosphere of Titan composed of?",
      "correctAnswer": "Oxygen 57%, Nitrogen 33%, Argon 6%, CO2 3%",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Nitrogen 70%, Oxygen 20%, Argon 10%", "Oxygen 60%, Helium 30%, Trace gases 10%", "Oxygen 50%, Nitrogen 40%, Carbon Dioxide 10%"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the leader of Ehana?",
      "correctAnswer": "High Lord Tacer",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Kahn Coars", "Xarendos", "Erros"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the total ground force of Recola?",
      "correctAnswer": "146 hexillion",
      "wrongAnswers": ["90 million", "1 trillion", "7 billion"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the population of Filto?",
      "correctAnswer": "45 trillion",
      "wrongAnswers": ["50 trillion", "60 trillion", "40 trillion"],
      "timeout": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the capital of Klesone?",
      "correctAnswer": "Rrinai",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Filoho", "Lumen City", "Nezon"],
      "timeout": 10
    }
  ],
  "time given": "10"
}

